http://www.cathouseclothing.com/pages/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Cathouse Clothing - Privacy NoticeThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from ww.cathouseclothing.com (the “Site”).Our Contact Information (Data Controller)AddressCathouse ClothingUnit 17, Victoria Spring Business Park, Wormald Street, Liversedge, West Yorkshire, WF15 6BUPhone+44 (0)1924 412 662Company Emailinfo@cathouseclothing.com Personal Information We CollectWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:"Cookies" are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies if needed, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. On Cathouse Clothing we add cookies to enable you to login to your Account securely, to let you see your recently browsed products, and to remember your shopping basket for you between visits to the website - therefore disabling cookies may prevent those features working."Log files" track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. This is a standard feature of web servers; at Cathouse Clothing we do not use any of this data for any marketing - other than in cases of fraud investigation it is only used to ensure reliability of the web server hosting this web site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information , email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.How Do We Use Your Personal InformationWe use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).Sharing of Personal InformationWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Worldpay to power our online store payment.We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Your RightsIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you have registered for an account you can view all the information we have stored about you and your orders by logging in to the My Account feature of the website. If you would like to exercise your rights, please contact us through the contact information on this page.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.Data RetentionWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.MinorsThe Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18ChangesWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.FinallyFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, if you would like to make a complaint, or if you would like to have all data associated with your account deleted, please contact us by e-mail at info@cathouseclothing.com or by mail using the details provided below:Cathouse ClothingUnit 17, Victoria Spring Business Park, Wormald Street, Liversedge, West Yorkshire, WF15 6BU
We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By browsing this website, you agree to our use of cookies.
Accept
More info
